Joel, you want to start us off?
>> Hey, Cam. Uh, what's uh what's your
relationship with Lou like? You know,
you guys been together for a long time.
>> All right, man. That's my dog. Uh,
that's all I can really say, man. Uh, I
think that's the one of the big reasons
that I'm here, man. We had a great
relationship while I was uh attending uh
the Bengals uh when they drafted me and
it's kind of been great ever since then.
uh when he gave me a call and had me
come up, I was very excited, man. I
can't wait for this opportunity.
>> Why do you think you guys Why do you
think you guys mesh so well together?
>> I think it's his scheme, man. He knows
my kind of gameplay and uh how tough
that uh he he loves his corners. Uh like
to come up and hit uh play manto man,
come down and you know, just play Grammy
football. And I think that's kind of the
way that I succeeded.
Anyone
else want to drop their name in the
chat? Kent, go ahead.
>> What are your uh what are your thoughts
just from the outside looking in where
the Colts are headed, how optimistic you
can be as a player that you're coming to
an organization that's ready to win.
>> Yeah, honestly, man, uh after seeing
last year and the guy the run that they
went on, uh you can say that they're on
the right track, man. I believe they did
have some missing pieces and I think I
come in and you know fill that void uh
where where it was needed.
>> Joel,
>> how long your foot? I know you had the
lift Frank injury last year.
>> Oh, it's good, man. I should be here
good soon. Uh all the way to go. Uh get
some things knocked out first here in
this couple uh this month here and then
you know it's all go time.
Nathan,
>> um know this is a team that has uh a
couple strong guys at quarterback and
Mooney Ward and and Sgardner. When you
look at this lineup, um I know you
can't, you know, tell us exactly what
you and Lou spoke about as far as your
future, but how do you envision you and
your skills fitting in with the group
that uh Indianapolis already has there
in the secondary?
>> I bring, you know, the athleticism. I
feel like I bring a different vibe from
the other guys. Uh they're very dynamic
in every way. Uh so most definitely I
feel like I could just fit in, you know,
and bring my my physicalness. Uh and
then and some ball skills, man.
>> Thanks,
>> Kevin.
>> Hey Cam, congrats. Um how much outside
versus slot did you play in Cincy?
>> I mainly play outside unless I was
playing manto man and I had to move into
the slot and follow the receiver.
And then um do you feel like you'll be
cleared for OTAAS or what's the spring
look like?
>> Yeah, I believe so. I guess sir.
>> All right, we'll do just a few more
chat.
>> Yeah, Cam, uh I know you had the injury
at the end of last year or end of last
year. Why did it just not work out
before the injury? It looked like you
weren't real happy in your playing time
decree. Was it just not meshing with the
new coordinator or what?
It didn't have anything to do with the
coordinator, man. Uh I would say I was
great in a sense. I believe it was most
definitely a personal thing with me and
uh I just couldn't get my head right and
I believe most definitely uh it showed
in my game and and you you don't put bad
film on the on the on the field and
that's what happened.
>> Thank you.
>> Yes, sir.
>> And last question, Lara
>> Cam, welcome to Indie. You mentioned
your familiarity with Lou. Um, do you
have much familiarity with the other
guys in your room? Guys like Kenny
Moore, we talked about, you know, Mooney
and Sauce. And then in your experiences,
how beneficial can it be to have a room
that you mentioned is dynamic and
physical? And obviously you guys can
compete against one another and really
elevate that group.
>> Yeah, I do know there are a lot of the
guys in the room already. Um, funny
story that me and Sauce, we train
together to become NFL players. Uh, so
we training exos together. So there's a
relationship there and uh you know and
and I believe you know it just like
receivers have a family I think DBs have
a family. So I know most of the guys in
the room but when I say uh they're very
dynamic man I think we're going to work
very well together. I think the
competitiveness will kind of push every
last one of us to our our extent to be
great and uh help this team you know
succeed.